[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "The article mentions that pangolins in Taiwan were hunted to near extinction. Which of the following is closest in meaning to near extinction?",
        "answer": "almost disappearing forever"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, in what year did Taiwan pass the Wildlife Conservation Act?",
        "answer": "1989"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following types of pangolin is increasing in number?",
        "answer": "the Formosan pangolin"
    },
    {
        "question": "The article uses a phrase so much so. Which of the following is closest in meaning to this phrase?",
        "answer": "It is used to indicate that an earlier statement is very true."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the countries that sent teams to study Taiwan's successful pangolin conservation was NOT mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? Taiwan has been successful in helping its pangolins from becoming extinct.",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following pangolin products is NOT mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "horns"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? Humans have been able to save every animal species in the world from becoming extinct.",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pangolins are also known by the name _____.",
        "answer": "scaly anteaters"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, pangolins are _____.",
        "answer": "one of the most illegally traded animals in the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, how many pangolins used to be exported from Taiwan each year?",
        "answer": "more than sixty thousand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following phrases in the article is used to indicate that an earlier statement is very true?",
        "answer": "so much so"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, what is one of the remaining dangers for Taiwan's wild pangolins?",
        "answer": "habitat loss"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does the writer seem to feel about Taiwan's pangolin conservation efforts?",
        "answer": "positive - very good"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is another name sometimes used for pangolins?",
        "answer": "the scaly anteater"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, _____ pangolins have been killed in the last ten years.",
        "answer": "over 1,000,000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the institutes researching pangolins was NOT mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "Academia Sinica"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, which of the following is no longer a danger for Taiwan's pangolins?",
        "answer": "people hunting them for their meat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following types of pangolin is NOT decreasing in number?",
        "answer": "the Formosan pangolin"
    },
    {
        "question": "The author seems to feel that Taiwan's pangolin conservation efforts have been _____.",
        "answer": "very successful"
    }
]